[
    {
        "id": 0,
        "question": "Which of the following syntax correctly declares an Array?",
        "options": [
            "int geeks;",
            "array geeks[20];",
            "geeks{20};",
            "int geeks[20];"
        ],
        "correctOption": "int geeks[20];",
        "points": 10
    },
    {
        "id": 1,
        "question": "The size of the array should always be _____",
        "options": [
            "Positive",
            "Negative",
            "Whole Number",
            "Real Number"
        ],
        "correctOption": "Positive",
        "points": 10
    },
    {
        "id": 2,
        "question": "What is the correct way to initialize values in an array?",
        "options": [
            "my_array [5] = (5,3,4,2,7);",
            "my_array [5] = {5;3;4;2;7};",
            "my_array [5] = {5,3,4,2,7,5,6,7,8};",
            "my_array [5] = {1,2,3,4,5}"
        ],
        "correctOption": "my_array [5] = {1,2,3,4,5}",
        "points": 10
    },
    {
        "id": 3,
        "question": "In an array int arr[3]={1,2,3}, what will happen if we try to access arr[4] in C/C++?",
        "options": [
            "Run Time Error",
            "3",
            "0",
            "Garbage value"
        ],
        "correctOption": "Garbage value",
        "points": 10
    },
    {
        "id": 4,
        "question": "Which of these operators can be used to concatenate two or more String objects?",
        "options": [
            "'+'",
            "'+='",
            "'&'",
            "None of these"
        ],
        "correctOption": "'+'",
        "points": 10
    },
    {
        "id": 5,
        "question": "Which of these methods of class String is used to obtain the length of the String object?",
        "options": [
            "get()",
            "Sizeof()",
            "lengthof()",
            "length()"
        ],
        "correctOption": "length()",
        "points": 10
    },
    {
        "id": 6,
        "question": "In a circular linked list, the last node points to the____.",
        "options": [
            "this pointer",
            "tall pointer",
            "first node",
            "middle node"
        ],
        "correctOption": "first node",
        "points": 20
    },
    {
        "id": 7,
        "question": "What advantage does a linked list have over an array?",
        "options": [
            "A linked list is not of a fixed size",
            "It's Better",
            "It's Easier to use",
            "A linked list can give you the data faster"
        ],
        "correctOption": "A linked list is not of a fixed size",
        "points": 30
    },
    {
        "id": 8,
        "question": "Nodes in a linked list contain two things:",
        "options": [
            "A pointer and a node",
            "A Pointer and a reference",
            "Direction and a pointer",
            "Data and a pointer"
        ],
        "correctOption": "Data and a pointer",
        "points": 20
    },
    {
        "id": 9,
        "question": "The last node of the singly-linked list contains ___",
        "options": [
            "NULL",
            "Next Pointer",
            "Data",
            "None of the above"
        ],
        "correctOption": "NULL",
        "points": 30
    }
]